

CONTACT ME

- andbardii@icloud.com
- 😯 Bologna, Emila Romagna
- + 39 3406027415
- in linkedin.com/in/andbardii

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- SCSS e SASS
- Bootstrap
- GIT
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Angular
- Java
- Spring
- Illustrator
- Photoshop
- Premiere Pro
- InDesign

LANGUAGES

- Italian
- English

ANDREA BARDI

Junior Full Stack Developer & Graphic Designer

PROFILE

My name is Andrea and I am a 20 years old boy, graduate with excellent marks in Graphics and Communication, now I have finished a high training course as a Full Stack Developer at Epicode.

I have always wanted to work in digital and I based my studies on this belief. In the coming years, however, I want to continue to train and research new technologies with which to test myself.

I'm looking for a junior position as front or back developer to apply and improve my skills.s, I will continue to train and look for new technologies to test myself.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Intern in graphic design department

November 2021 - December 2021

Comet Spa - Bologna, Emilia Romagna

November 2020 - December 2020

Grafiche e Liquori Snc - San Lazzaro di Savena, Emilia Romagna

Skills: InDesign · Premiere · Photoshop · Illustrator

Rider

August 2021 - December 2021

Just Eat - Bologna, Emilia Romagna

October 2020 - August 2021

Deliveroo - Bologna, Emilia Romagna

Skills: Problem Solving

EDUCATION

Epicode School

Post Diploma Course as Full Stack Developer

Skills: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Firebase, Java, Spring

Responsive website development, single-page applications development, relational database development, REST API services development, OOP programming, security development, test management.

Istitituto Aldini Valeriani

High School Diploma in Graphic Design and Communication

Grade: 100/100

Skills: InDesign · Premiere · Photoshop · Illustrator

Design advertising campaigns and realization of advertising on various media, rebranding, packaging design, production of audio and video commercials.

According to Legislative Decree 101/2018 and art. 13 of the GDPR (EU Regulation 2016/679) authorize the processing of my personal data in the curriculum vita